How are you?
Hello! Ste this time with Rika Shimakura of Beyonce Subway,
Natsumi Nakayama of Ocha no Momo.
This time, we are going to present you with the two of us, so please bear with us until the end.
Actually, we are both trainee members of Halo Pro.
They joined the Halo Pro trainees about 7 years ago.
Seven years ago.
I didn't realize it had been that long,
I was surprised to hear your story today.
Do you remember? About those days.
What I remember most vividly from back then is..,
I was in the 5th grade when I joined the Halo Pro trainees,
It was hard for me to use honorifics and apologize properly,
I remember I was always relying on Rika Shimakura.
I was the oldest among my classmates and Natsumi was the youngest.
So there was a huge age difference between us,
We got along quite well,
I took lessons in Tokyo,
I took lessons in Tokyo, and Natsumi took lessons in Osaka,
We had lessons as separate teams,
We didn't see each other that often,
We didn't see each other that often, but when we saw each other occasionally at live performances, Natsumi would come up to me and look at me,
We were very close.
I imagine that she would listen to me talk about unimportant things.
We talked a lot.
We were in elementary school.
An elementary school student and a high school student.
You are so cute.
Thank you very much.
Beyonce's spring tour will start on April 7 in Hiroshima.
It will be Beyonce's first live house tour.
I see.
Because the hall tour was earlier than the live house tour,
So I'm really looking forward to having fun with you all in a live house at a close distance.
And then, Ochanomomo Ochanomomo Live Tour 2024!
Our hometown is Japan, and the tour will start on April 7 in Osaka as well.
We, Ochanomomo, have been touring around the 47 prefectures of Japan since last year 2023,
We are going to start the tour from Osaka on April 7, This is a restart version of that show, so we will start with the Osaka performance,
I would be happy if you could come and see us, not only in Osaka, but also in your neighborhood.
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
The Tea Ceremony
You say you're going out, but you don't go out.
I don't go out.
You say you're going out, and then you don't go out.
You're late getting ready
One step at a time
Do-do-do-do all the way
Let's go to town
Rumble, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle
Shutters again
I know what it's like
I know, but your mom just apologized to me.
She apologized to me.
That's a lie.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what the future holds.
Look, it's over without me.
If you smash him...
you'll be a man
a natural beheading
this too plays to the sound of regret
hey, i'm drunk with myself too
Spoiled head
Absolute man
Wow wow yeah yeah
Big and perfect
I'm the last one to fail
You're mine
I'm pretty excited about this.
I'm gonna make it go away.
That's what I'm talking about.
I knew this would happen.
I knew it.
We'll meet at the station. We'll set a time. I should have waited in front of the station.
I should have waited.
Still, I clicked.
I've been looking at the menu.
I'm looking at them.
Oh, my God, this looks so good.
I'm in awe.
Wow!
Comedy Central.
I don't need this.
I can't wait to see what happens next week.
I make plans and then they fall apart
I don't want to be born again
I've got a lot of scrap metal.
That's a lot of words.
Still, it's more than just a personality
The town dialect is not big enough
I'll just have to educate them somewhere else
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
What do you mean "big pappé"?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Just leave it at that.
We want to do it right, don't we?
Build it big!
That's right.
I can't imagine what the future holds
You know, without me, you're finished.
I'm the only one who can do it
test, answer, lie
That too plays on my regrets
Hey, I'm drunk on myself too
The reason I'm sweet on you is because you're a genius
Wow Wow Hey Hey
The world is perfect
You know, I don't know why I'm so nervous
It's always you
But I can't help but hope for the best But I'm hopeful.
Keep going out and doing what you're doing.
Soaker show.
I love you for trying so hard.
Beyonds Rika Shimokura of Subway and Natsume Nakayama of Tea Aunt are presenting Halo! sta.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer at a quick pace.
Tomorrow is February 29th. What comes for Natsume once every four years or so?
When the desire to get a short cut comes. One year ago on this day, I performed at the Nippon Budokan as the opening act for JuiceJuice.
What do you think Ocha-no-Ma has evolved the most in the past year? Ability to cope
It's graduation season for students. What is Hello Project's graduation song for Natsume? Aya Matsuura's "Chillin' in the Cold
What is your favorite food?
Shirako ponzu and Nohara cartilage.
Natsume's hometown, Kagawa Onsenkyo, is currently hosting a Hello Project project.
Here are some of the best things about Kagawa Onsenkyo at this time of year!
You'll be able to experience the hot springs, the food, and the kindness of the town's people.
I often like to take a shortcut once every four years.
I see.
I haven't had my hair cut shorter than my collarbones since I was born.
It's always been long.
It's not that I don't like long hair, of course. I like long hair.
I like long hair and I have long hair, but sometimes I want to cut it short, like once every four years or so.
So I bought a wig just the other day.
I bought a bob wig and tried it.
It was well received by my supporters.
I'm actually thinking about cutting it this year.
I've done it before.
You bought a wig and went long?
I went short.
How'd it go? It was a little iffy.
I'd like to try it.
I don't think I'd have the courage.
Next, I asked you what your favorite food was.
Albacore with ponzu sauce.
Recently, I like to watch ASMR videos of big eaters on social networking sites.
This person was eating Shirako Ponzu, and that's how I got hooked on it.
The reason I heard about this is because I've been talking about going out to eat with Matsumai for a long time.
I asked him what he likes as a kind of research.
I'm an adult. Adult.
I was just thinking that's what you're supposed to do.
That's exactly why I've been saying we should go for a few years.
But it's been a scam for a long time.
I'd like to go this year.
The question of understanding came after the VTR.
Hello! Sta!
Getchu!
Halo! Ste!
Next, I would like to ask Rika a question
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll try my best!
This year, Rika is the new year's daughter.
What Showa era song would be a good theme song for Mr. Tatsuta?
Yes, let's see...
Judy Young's song.
Today, February 28th, is Baka Bastard Day!
What is the latest event that made you want to yell "asshole" at yourself?
Well, I bought a new lipstick.
I bought a new lipstick and lost it a week or so later.
What's one thing you're not going to do in 2023?
Fishing!
What do you definitely want to do in 2024? Diving!
This August marks the 5th anniversary of Beyoncé's debut. What is different from what you imagined yourself to be five years ago?
My face? I didn't think I would look this different.
Thank you very much. I see. So, first of all, I would like to ask you, in what ways are you different from the person you imagined yourself to be five years ago?
Your face has not changed. Yes, we watch videos of those days together, and I look like the same person I was yesterday.
I was the only one who looked the same as I did yesterday. I was sometimes told, "Rika is the only one who hasn't changed. I see.
Yes, I feel like I am the same person I was when I was a little less made-up. But it is true that from the time I met Rika until now.
I haven't changed that much since I was a trainee. Yes, I haven't changed my hairstyle or anything, so I imagined that I would have changed more, but surprisingly, I haven't. That's the good thing.
That's the good thing. Thank you.
Next, I wanted to ask you a question about your unfinished business in 2023, which is fishing.
I went fishing once by myself the year before last and had a great time. I wanted to do it again, but I didn't have a chance to do it last year, so I would like to do it this year. I would like to do it this year.
Natsume, I like fishing a lot and used to do it at my parents' house, so let's go fishing together next time. Fishing? I want to fish.
Actually, I don't know that much about it, but I think we can do it if we do it together.
Hello! Stee, we'll continue after this.
Next up is a presentation of lyrics that touched my heart. Hello Project has a lot of great songs, but this time it's the season of graduation and departures, so I thought I'd share some of the lyrics and phrases that came to mind.
I was moved to tears by Aya Matsuura's smile. What lyrics or phrases came to your mind? I cried because of Aya Matsuura's smile.
Thank you Dear My Friends.
The lyrics "I'll see you again, I'm sure we'll see each other again" are very meaningful to me because I know there are kids who move to a different area after graduating from high school or junior high school.
I thought it was a good idea to say "we'll see each other again" to express the meaning of the song.
This song was the first song we performed when we joined the Halo Pro trainees.
I was told by my teacher that I could perform this song if I could learn it perfectly, but I couldn't dance to it because I couldn't dance to it in a good tail, which was a bit frustrating for me.
So I chose this song.
Yes, I chose Morning Musume's "Tears Can't Stop After School".
The last part of the lyrics, "I can't stop crying because you're too kind, I can't stop crying because I'm too happy," is so humble and cute.
It's such a humble and lovely poem.
Haruna Ogata sang it solo at the end of her graduation concert, and I knew it was a great song.
I knew it was a great song, but I also remember thinking it was a great song.
I remember I thought it was a great song, and I remember the tone of his voice was great.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello! Project's songs that have touched our hearts and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Yukiho Shimoita ni Yukiho, will be presenting the lyrics of the song.
Thank you for meeting me.
This is Tomoyo in angst.
This is Kazu.
I'm not going to talk.
I've been talking too much and I can't talk about yuppie.
Please talk.
What did you think when you saw the lyrics?
I'm very curious,
Please comment.
It reminded me of a friend from junior high school,
I know, right?
The members I met in Angelem are the same,
Project, and also the older members of Hello!
Project, and I am really happy that I met them,
It was right around the time of my graduation.
I was graduating from junior high school,
When I heard it again,
It really touched me,
I cried,
I cried, and I left him, even though he was so precious to me,
I left him in high school. High School.
That's the most important thing,
But I like the idea of being irreplaceable.
You know what I mean?
Why are you crying?
When I saw the lyrics, I thought, "Ah!
I didn't hear it at all.
I'm laughing.
Oh, my God. What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I can understand why you're crying.
It's not that this song reminds me of someone,
I think the lyrics of this song really resonate with me,
I think it's a song to deliver.
I've seen a lot of seniors singing this song when they graduate,
I think it is a song that only Angulum can sing,
I think this song is a lyric that belongs to Angulum and can be included in the group.
I'm glad. I understand. I totally understand.
Thank you.
I really understand.
Because these are nothing but good lyrics.
And the song is sung by the leader,
Until now, the leader of the group sang this song,
But before that, the members who were graduating sang this part.
It's not good, is it?
So it's really like an emo song.
But this phrase doesn't cut it late.
Because all the lyrics are good.
Just "Yes! Yes! We are flame!
Forever!
You know? It's like empathy.
Whenever I sing "Tomoyo", I always think that Ange is very youthful.
I think that when I listen to it.
Because, you know, we're in a circle,
Yes! Yes! We are flame!
And I hear that this moment is only for now,
But we are flame! But because We are flame!
I sometimes feel that I don't want it to fade in my memory.
I can't fit it all in one place,
And Hanane, too. Because the first tear came out.
No, it's not.
Thank you for doing it.
Thank you very much.
Well, that's all for this time.
Look forward to the next installment!
Beyond! Rika Shimakura from Subway and Natsumi Nakayama from Ochanomizu,
Natsumi Nakayama from Ochanomizu, and Rika Shimakura from Subway, will be presenting Halo! Subway's Rika Shimakura and Natsumi Nakayama of Ochamama.
As I mentioned in the opening, we are two trainees in the same class,
We are two trainees in the same class.
What do you think of each other's performance?
How do you see each other's performance now?
I, Nakayama, have seen Beyond!
I've seen them perform live many times, and I've seen Rika Shimakura perform,
Rika Shimakura has a very clear voice,
I admire her voice and her singing,
I'm happy.
I think it's great,
I admire the way she sings, especially the high notes, and the way she sings without feeling the difference in pitch,
I also admire the way you approach your performance.
I am glad.
I can recognize Natsume anywhere on stage.
Really?
She has a nice smile and a great style, so it's easy to spot her.
I've loved Natsume's dancing since she joined the group,
You've grown taller, too.
She has grown taller, that's for sure.
I see her standing on stage looking even better, so I think it's wonderful.
The way she keeps her hair in place is also really cool.
I'm glad. We don't usually talk about this kind of thing, so it was really fresh and I was happy.
This time, I chose a live video of the other group's music, which is very exciting,
I will introduce them in order.
I chose "Yoridorimidori" as my favorite Ochanoma song.
Let's look at the video of Ochanoma Concert Tour 2023 Spring Growing Up together.
I love Valan's part so much. I love Valin's part so much.
I mean, look at the lines and stuff.
Yeah.
He's so cute.
Wiener.
Cute.
A song that can do amazing listening and listening with the fans.
Among the songs of Ajanorman.
I know.
I think the fans love it a lot.
It's a great excitement.
I like this part.
It's really shaking up.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes, it is. They're whooping.
It's a really fun song,
It's a fun song.
It's easy to dance to and sing,
I'm surprised that there are no setlists without this song in live performances or tours,
That's right.
It's a song we play often.
It's easy to see.
I think we did a live show at Chanoma with Mr. Bunbun a long time ago.
I think we played it then, too.
This Yaridorimidori has a part to call out,
I also thought Risa Hiroshi's cones were so beautiful and exciting,
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
I can hear the fans hooting and hollering.
That's for sure.
That's why I chose it.
I'm glad.
You know, this song was the phrase of the song without only Muscat's voice,
So, Muscat, no compromise, me, Viva, and so many other fruit names are mentioned.
I thought it was a fruit song.
So I said, "I wonder how many fruits appear in this song and how many times they appear in this song,
So they were looking for it,
It's fun.
I hope you will try to find them, too. I encourage everyone to look for it.
Hallo! Ste.
My choice for the most exciting Beyonce song is
Hot! I'm going to be performing it at the Beyonce concert tour.
Beyonce Concert Tour
Let's watch the video of Neo-Beyo at Budokan together.
I was in the audience at this concert,
I think this was the first time for Beyond to perform live alone.
It was around this time that he started to perform his voice at the concert,
I felt the power of this song,
I wanted to see it again this time.
I'm glad.
It's an easy song to sing.
I was happy to hear that many of you introduced the song to the audience.
I was watching from the second floor seats,
I was watching from the second floor seats, and I could see what was going on on the first floor.
I could see what was going on on the first floor, and the people on the first floor were cutting off their heads like crazy,
I thought it would be fun for me to be there,
I thought it would be fun for me to be there.
They are using a lot of customization.
I realized that there is customization here.
I see.
It's the same kind of customization you always use.
Yes, yes, yes.
I realized that no matter how many times I see this song, I can still get excited and enjoy it with the audience as one.
I'm glad.
The next song on this tour is the one that uses castanets, and it's called Tears of Castanets.
It was a little unusual because we were going to play "Tears of Castanets," and we had to hold the castanets while we were playing "Hot,
So, I was just going along with it.
I was doing it. That's nice.
Oh, that's nice.
It was a little bit unusual.
ED.
I wish I could stay behind for the invitation.
I'm sorry, I'll see you today.
Heart, bouncing sound
A little horse cloud in front of the big wind
Happiness jumps to you Jumping for Happiness
Adorana
Around the turnstiles on the West Road
I'm heading there as fast as I can.
A little kiss kiss kiss.
I'm so happy for you.
It's more exciting on short notice.
All white, all white, all white.
Your card will stand out.
My turn.
I'm totally squeamish, squeamish, squeamish
Exciting Temptation
Very, very romance
We can't get enough of the heartbeat
We can ride
Sukisuki Sukisuki
The lure of the water stops piling up
Everyone looks up
voices passing each other
I love you
A little kiss is in between
Electronic sounds, clitics, swaying, swaying, adjusting the senses.
What's that, mama shoka?
I'm not trying to match. I'm just trying to make it easier for you to get there.
Making love car, no balance tonight.
And the toilet's heavenly.
Tomorrow, the sisters will make up their minds.
Fanta-nan, Fanta-nan, Fanta-nan
I want to dream of you and me
while the city lights up here and where we're going
time is passing us by
I see the sparkle in your eyes
I can't play more with you
Chosa sa kikkuri kikkuri
rufufuremensi osharei
the more sudden the better
I made it into a weeping weeping weeping
Why don't you take a ride, really? Why don't you try it?
I'm going for it, it's my turn
I totally love it, love it, love it
Seduction, seduction, seduction
Very, very romance
Keep it up.
It gets harder and harder
Suki Suki Suki
Seino, it's Tsubaki Factory!
The launch event at Club Twitter has come to an end.
And on February 29th, the day this event took place, we celebrated the 7th anniversary of Tsubaki Factory's major debut.
7th anniversary.
We have celebrated our 7th anniversary, then, Mizuho.
But really, it's already been 8 years?
We are.
I was talking with Sakkiruno, and she said that when we made our major debut, we were still carrying our school bags on our backs.
Wow!
That's right.
Now we are working together as members,
So I really think that Tsubaki Factory has changed in many ways over time, and now we have become the strongest,
I am glad to have met you all.
Yes, Taruno-chan is carrying such a school bag on her back.
Yes, I have not actually celebrated the 7th anniversary,
But I was thinking that it was our 7th anniversary since we joined the group, and I was thinking that it was our 5th anniversary just recently.
So it has been 2 years?
Eight years?
That's for sure.
That's right.
I felt that time has passed very quickly,
And I am looking forward to celebrating our 8th and 9th anniversaries in the future,
I would like to grow up a little more than when we celebrated our 7th anniversary.
It would be nice.
It's good to show what's ahead.
I celebrated my 7th anniversary last year,
It is not a matter of course that we can celebrate with all the members every year like this,
I think we were able to celebrate our 7th anniversary because we received a lot of love from everyone,
I would like to continue to do my best to be a group that is loved even more and more by everyone.
Tsubaki Factory has just released its 3rd album "3rd Moment". And Tsubaki Factory has released its 3rd album, 3rd Moment.
What do you recommend for 3rd Moment?
Saori-chan.
Yes, I'm Saori-chan. I was on the stage at the Halo! I was up on the stage at the Halo!
There is a song called "Power Floor, Now is the time to be united! This song is a song that can be performed with call and response,
This song is a song that allows for call and response,
This song is a song that allows for call and response, and there are parts where you can really shout out a lot of "hey" and "oi oi oi",
I hope everyone can enjoy the song as one.
Kyumi.
I knew you would come.
What do you recommend for the album?
I think there are a lot of pieces that give you a sense of Tsubaki Factory's history, and I would like to recommend the live new song "Seventh Blooming",
I would like to recommend a new live song called Shichibunsaki no Tsuguhatsu,
I would like to recommend a new live song called "Shichibunsaki no Tsuguhatsu" (Continuation of Seven Minutes in Bloom), which I think is a perfect song for spring,
It has a very cute tune,
I would like you to listen to it in spring,
I would like you to listen to it in spring when you go for a walk or something.
It's so lovely!
Tsubaki Factory has many songs that really make you feel the season,
I hope everyone can listen to this album and feel the various moments of the season,
I hope that you will listen to this album as much as possible while feeling the season and the various moments.
So, please listen to Tsubaki Factory's 3rd album, 3rd Moment,
Please listen to it as much as you can.
That's all for now, Tsubaki Factory!
Rika Shimakura of Beyonce Subway and
Natsumi Nakayama of Ocha-no-Ma presents "Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here is an announcement!
Beyonce will be starring in the play
Beyonce stars in the stage play "Biospy, Theatre Girls Club".
will be released on March 27th!
This play is about a spy.
This is the first time to challenge an action scene.
It's also a very funny play with laughter and tears.
It is a very interesting stage with laughter and tears.
I think you will be able to see many details of the action scenes
I think you will be able to see a lot of details of the action scenes on Blu-ray. I'm sure you'll see a lot of it.
Please check it out!
And Biophonic 2 will be
Tokyo performance on April 6
Kobe performance will be held on May 10.
This one will be performed live by an orchestra.
Beyonce's music will be performed live by an orchestra.
This is a very, very gorgeous concert!
Finally, the concert will be held not only in Tokyo, but also in Kobe.
I'm nervous, but I'm really looking forward to it.
I will do my best!
And Beyonce's spring tour will start
Beyonce's spring tour will start on April 7 in Hiroshima!
This will be Beyonce's first live house tour.
This will be the first live house tour for Beyonce, so we will be closer to you than ever before.
You will be able to enjoy the live performance with us at a closer distance than ever before.
We hope to see you there!
And Ocha-no-Ma Live Tour 2024
Our hometown is Japan! will start from the Osaka show on April 7.
will start on April 7 in Osaka!
This will be the first time this year that Ochanoma will be touring alone.
and it will be the first tour this year for Ochanomama alone.
We have been touring around 47 prefectures since last year.
This time, the first day of the tour will be in Osaka.
If you are in the area, please come and visit us.
If you are in the area and have time to visit us, we would be very happy if you could come and see us.
We are looking forward to seeing you!
And from Ocha-no-Ma
March 24, Ochanoma Kataria Presents: Pop Culture Live!
We will be performing at Pop Culture Live!
We are looking forward to seeing you at the live event.
It's a little different from the usual live performance of Ochanoma.
I think you will be able to experience a slightly different atmosphere
Please come and join us!
We will be performing at Makuhari Messe on March 30th and 31st.
Think Carbon Neutral
2024 by Satomi Satoyama Movement will be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
will be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.The event is scheduled to be held!
Please come and visit us!
The "Hello! Project members will appear on this channel
Project members will appear on the channel more and more!
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time, we will be talking with
Rika Shimakura from Beyonds Subway
and Natsumi Nakayama of Ocha-no-Ma.
Good bye.